<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Easy Money | Jagmohan Singh]]></title>
  <link href="http://jagmohansingh.github.io/blog/categories/easy-money/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://jagmohansingh.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-19T14:00:39+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://jagmohansingh.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jagmohan Singh]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[PaisaSwipe: Earn Money while unlocking your Android Device]]></title>
    <link href="http://jagmohansingh.github.io/2013/12/14/paisaswipe-earn-money-while-unlocking-your-android-device/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-14T20:27:16+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://jagmohansingh.github.io/2013/12/14/paisaswipe-earn-money-while-unlocking-your-android-device</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="right" src="/images/app-home.png" width="240" height="320" title="PaisaSwipe" >
Have you ever looked at an advertisement that&rsquo;s trying to sell you something and thought, <strong>They should be paying me to look at this</strong>. Well, now all your sarcastic dreams can come true with a new Android app from India, <a href="http://paisaswipe.com/home/">PaisaSwipe</a>.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s pretty simple. Each time you swipe it away, an amount multiple 10paisa is deposited into your PaisaSwipe account. You can earn up to Rs. 300 per month, and possibly more if you get your friends to sign up. As the app description says, <strong>It is the easiest money you will ever make.</strong></p>

<p>According to PaisaSwipe, with 10,000+ downloads and a rating of 4.3 out of 5 in the first month of the launch, the App is currently seeing 1,000 downloads a day, has crossed 4 million Ad impressions and is witnessing at least 100,000 ad impressions per day. The other &lsquo;plus&rsquo; is users get curated Ad content, depending on their interests. The &lsquo;relevance&rsquo;, the &lsquo;control&rsquo; (one can choose not to &lsquo;swipe&rsquo; the Ads) and the &lsquo;reward&rsquo; parts are the unique triggers that will further drive mobile marketing, says PaisaSwipe.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p><a href="http://paisaswipe.com/home/">PaisaSwipe</a> says similar apps like <a href="http://www.cashslide.co.kr/">Cash Slide</a> in South Korea and <a href="http://www.getlocket.com/">Locket</a> in the USA have been very successful. Like its American and Korean counterparts, it&rsquo;s only available domestically, but is looking to expand to other countries in the near future.</p>

<p>Still in Beta, the app has already signed up big clients like McDonald&rsquo;s and KFC for one-month free trial runs. PaisaSwipe hopes to get 100,000 users this month and raise $1 Million in investment over the next six months.</p>

<p>If you&rsquo;re in India and you&rsquo;d like to give PaisaSwipe a try, you can download it on <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.paisaswipe.android">Google Play</a>. You can cash out either with PayPal, get FreeCharge mobile recharge coupons, or even donate the money to charity. Korean and American users can check out <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.cashslide">CashSlide</a> and <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.locket.android">Locket</a>, respectively.</p>

<h3>User Reviews</h3>


<p><i>Source: Google Play</i></p>

<p><blockquote><p><i>There was a time when people used to get frustrated by seeing Ads on their mobile screen, and now my friends get frustrated if they don&rsquo;t see Ads on their mobile screen&hellip;! Well done PaisaSwipe :)</i></p><footer><strong>Mridul Sen</strong></footer></blockquote>
<blockquote><p><i>Amazing Ads, I love the Ads, they are truly useful. Not just am I being given credits for viewing Ads but double credits for seeing them. Brilliant App!!!</i></p><footer><strong>Loy Veigas</strong></footer></blockquote>
<blockquote><p><i>All promises fulfilled! The quick response and fulfillment of all the made promises makes this App a must download. Developers are doing a great job here :)</i></p><footer><strong>Viraj Khetle</strong></footer></blockquote></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
